[Music]
two years is nothing but at the same
time
a lot can be accomplished in two years
you can try a sport you've always wanted
to start
and become great at it you can start a
morning routine
and affect your mood and stress at a
deep level you can meditate for a few
minutes per day
become more self-aware and change the
way you react to problems
you can start a business and make it a
big success
two years is nothing and extremely easy
to waste
but with small actions substantial
commitment
and consistency you can make it count
a lot two years being passive is a blink
of an eye
two years moving towards goals every
single day is plenty of time
it's just a matter of perspective there
is nothing that cannot be accomplished
in two years
with enough effort
you are not too old for the things you
were dreaming of doing when you were a
kid
you can still do extreme sports if you
wish to you can start playing a musical
instrument
you can become a photographer in two
years from now
you'll be great at it if you really want
to
don't let your past dictate who you are
you don't have to be the same person
you have always been don't let fear
control you
don't let the social standards conform
you age
is just a number we should all empower
our uniqueness
and fight against our own limitations
by doing things you love on a daily
basis
even for a few minutes you'll learn to
enjoy the journey
the days will become more than just a
means to an end
you'll see yourself evolving
[Music]
if you have the choice between feeling
great energetic
and in a positive mood versus feeling
sleepy
and moody what would you choose it's
just a choice
which combined with small even tiny
actions
like reducing meat or alcohol
consumption
or simply drinking more water walking
the stairs
or biking to the office you can do
wonders
it's not about the end goal it's about
daily actions
towards it it's also the reason why
morning routines
or 10 minutes daily meditation sessions
are bringing such great changes in terms
of mood
productivity stress management etc
replace tv shows and movies by
documentaries and books
monitor your days more get in control of
how you spend your time
take back the control of your health
mood
and time practice gratefulness
see the results in two years
be kind with people start with your
family
don't go mad one more time stop judging
see the good in them and remember that
you love them more than
anything in your working life being kind
and nice
can bring you more respect from people
who surround you than being bossy
and aggressive learn to say no often
for the right reasons people will accept
it more
and value your yes more because your
times value
will increase you don't need to be scary
to be respected
it's about building trust and healthy
long-term relationships
try this and in two years from now your
reality will be
so different silence your ego
love and trust others enough for two
years
harvest for 10 years or more
it has a lot to do with setting goals
but goals with our actions
are just wishes the easiest way to reach
goals is through daily and consistent
small
even tiny actions it's all about
consistency
commitment and regularity success
is not an event it's a process and a
mindset
small actions are putting you in the
position of succeeding
small actions make huge differences
look at yourself in the mirror in two
years and you'll think
that was quick every day
counts
you